{
  "questions" : {
    "history" : {
      "q0" : {
        "alts" : [
          "Egyptian",
          "Babylonian",
          "Chinese"
        ],
        "answer" : "Mesopotamian",
        "question" : "Which culture invented the plow?",
        "time" : 7
      },
      "q1" : {
        "alts" : [
          "6 April 1453",
          "14 October 1066",
          "30 April 1450"
        ],
        "answer" : "29 May 1453",
        "question" : "When was the city of Constatinople (Istanbul) conqured by Sultan Mehmed II?",
        "time" : 12
      }
    },
    "nature" : {
      "q0" : {
        "alts":[
          "Pineapple",
          "Papaya",
          "Kiwi"
        ],
        "answer" : "Mango",
        "question" : "Poison ivy belongs to a diverse botanical family that also includes the cashew and what tropical fruit?",
        "time" : 12
      }
    },
    "science" : {
      "q0" : {
        "alts":[
          "Venus",
          "Jupiter",
          "Earth"
        ],
        "answer" : "Mars",
        "question" : "Which planet is the 4th from the sun?",
        "time" : 7
      }
    },
    "celebrities" : {
      "q0" : {
        "alts":[
          "Ryan Reynolds",
          "Leonardo DiCaprio",
          "Johnny Depp"
        ],
        "answer" : "Nicholas Cage",
        "question" : "Known for his reckless spending, what movie star once paid $276,000 for a dinosaur skull?",
        "time" : 7
      }
    },
    "test" : {
      "q0" : {
        "alts" : [
          "alla ostar",
          "några ostar",
          "många ostar"
        ],
        "answer" : "inga ostar",
        "question" : "Hur många ostar har Johan hemma?",
        "time" : 20
      },
      "q1" : {
        "alts" : [
          "Test2",
          "Test3",
          "Test4"
        ],
        "answer" : "Test1",
        "question" : "Test",
        "time" : 1
      },
      "q2" : {
        "alts" : [
          "Test2",
          "Test3",
          "Test4"
        ],
        "answer" : "Test1",
        "question" : "Test",
        "time" : 1
      },
      "q3" : {
        "alts" : [
          "Test2",
          "Test3",
          "Test4"
        ],
        "answer" : "Test1",
        "question" : "Test",
        "time" : 1
      },
      "q4" : {
        "alts" : [
          "Test2",
          "Test3",
          "Test4"
        ],
        "answer" : "Test1",
        "question" : "Test",
        "time" : 1
      }
    },
    "literature" : {
      "q0" : {
        "alts" : [
          "Natsume Sõseki",
          "Junichirõ Tanizaki",
          "Akutagawa Ryunosuke"
        ],
        "answer" : "Osamu Dazai",
        "question" : "No longer human is one of Japans most populat novels and was writen shortly before it's authors suicide. Who was the author?",
        "time" : 12
      },
      "q1" : {
        "alts" : [
          "The setting sun",
          "Quicksand",
          "Kõjin"
        ],
        "answer" : "Kokoro",
        "question" : "Natsume Sõseki is often seen as on of Japans most influential authors becuase of one of hist works, What is the titel of this book?",
        "time" : 12
      }
    },
    "movies" : {
      "q0" : {
        "alts" : [
          "Make the music happen, Sam",
          "Music now, Sam",
          "Once more, Sam"
        ],
        "answer" : "Play it, Sam.",
        "question" : "What is the actual line of dialogue in “Casablanca”that is often misquoted as “Play it again, Sam”?",
        "time" : 7
      }
    },
    "music" : {

    },
    "sports" : {
      "q0" : {
        "alts" : [
          "13 hours, 10 min",
          "23 hours , 59 min",
          "3 hours, 23 min"
        ],
        "answer" : "11 hours, 5 min",
        "question" : "Played at Wimbledon in 2010, the longest match in tennis history lasted how long?",
        "time" : 7
      }
    },
    "geography" : {
      "q0" : {
        "alts" : [
          "Holland",
          "England",
          "Spain"
        ],
        "answer" : "The Netherlands",
        "question" : "New Zealand is named after a province in what nation?",
        "time" : 7
      }
    },
    "gaming" : {
      "q0" : {
        "alts" : [
          "Bonneter",
          "Cappers",
          "Tiara"
        ],
        "answer" : "Cappy",
        "question" : "In Mario Odyssey Mario is joined by a friendly hat. What is the name of this hat?",
        "time" : 10
      }
    },
    "religion" : {
      "q0" : {
        "alts" : [
          "Hinduism",
          "Taoism",
          "Shintoism"
        ],
        "answer" : "Buddhism",
        "question" : "In what religion is the Dhammapada a holy scripture?",
        "time" : 10
      }
    },
    "language" : {
      "q0" : {
        "alts" : [
          "Squirrel",
          "Man",
          "Bourgeois dog"
        ],
        "answer" : "Lady",
        "question" : "In a 1971 hit song,Tom Jones sings “Whoa!Whoa!Whoa! She’s a ” what?",
        "time" : 10
      }
    }
  },
  "items" : {
    "i0" : {
      "price" : 150,
      "type" : "Buff",
      "name" : "Double Score",
      "img_name" : "double_score",
      "scoreMultiplier" : 2,
      "timeHeadstart" : 0,
      "amountOfAlternatives" : 0
    },
    "i1" : {
      "price" : 120,
      "type" : "Buff",
      "name" : "Time Headstart",
      "img_name" : "time_headstart",
      "scoreMultiplier" : 1,
      "timeHeadstart" : 5,
      "amountOfAlternatives" : 0
    },
    "i2" : {
      "price" : 100,
      "type" : "Buff",
      "name" : "Fifty Fifty",
      "img_name" : "fifty_fifty",
      "scoreMultiplier" : 1,
      "timeHeadstart" : 0,
      "amountOfAlternatives" : 2
    },
    "i3" : {
      "price" : 100,
      "type" : "Debuff",
      "name" : "Half Score",
      "img_name" : "half_score",
      "scoreMultiplier" : 1,
      "timeHeadstart" : 0,
      "amountOfAlternatives" : 0
    },
    "i4" : {
      "price" : 80,
      "type" : "Debuff",
      "name" : "Time is money",
      "img_name" : "double_time",
      "scoreMultiplier" : 1,
      "timeHeadstart" : -5,
      "amountOfAlternatives" : 0
    },
    "i5" : {
      "price" : 80,
      "type" : "Debuff",
      "name" : "Let the robot do it",
      "img_name" : "binoculars",
      "scoreMultiplier" : 1,
      "timeHeadstart" : 0,
      "amountOfAlternatives" : 0
    }
  }
}
